CONTACT

PrazilRio de Janeiro

WhatsApp +55 (21) 99849-7373

🖆 Email

lukas-domingos1@hotmail.com

Portfolio

https://portfolio.mosalito.com/ https://github.com/lukas-loto https://www.linkedin.com/in/lu kas-domingos/

FORMATION

2021 - Atual **UFRJ**

2018 - 2021 CEFET/RJ Programação

LANGUAGES

Portuguese (mother tongue)

English (advanced)

Spanish (Basic)

INTEREST

WordPress Developer

Frontend Developer

PHP Developer

Full Stack Developer

Lukas Domingos

Full Stack Developer

PROFILE

Full Stack Developer with 4 years of experience specializing in WordPress.

My skills are: TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript frameworks like Next.js and React, WordPress, PHP frameworks like Codeigniter 4 and Laravel and Node. But I already had contact with other languages like Python, Java, C# and C++.

EXPERIENCE

April 2022 - Current Full Stack Web Developer, Virginia, United States

- Developed the new Webera website on WordPress
- I Developed the frontend of the Greenmainframe website in React/TypeScript
- I developed the Greenmainframe blog in WordPress
- Developed the Beer with the Boss website
- Developed the Mototalk website
- Vector design in Adobe Illustrator
- Image design in Canva and Photoshop
- · Versioning on GitHub and GitLab
- Production of modern landing pages
- Code and/or Zapier API integrations
- Creation of animations in After Effects for the frontend
- Use of Webhooks
- Use of microservices and microfrontends
- UI/UX application
- · Agile Methodology

April 2020 - April 2021 Full Stack Web Developer, Robo da Loto, Brazil

- Reproduction of Figma layouts with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and jQuery
- Use of Trello for Agile Methodology
- Versioning on GitHub
- Development in PHP/Codeigniter 4

April 2019 - April 2020 Full Stack Web Developer, Freelance

- Creation of e-commerce, blog with Frontend Publishing, landing page, and websites in general.
- Rest API, Node, React, Javascript, PHP/Codeigniter 4, Json, C, C#, C++, Python, Java, HTML, and CSS.
- Automation and notification of messages from leads by robots via WhatsApp with its own server using Baileys API

April 2019 - April 2020 Full Stack Web Developer, Internship

• API development for 1 year in Node.js and Python to generate the Federal College and College electronic time attendance sheet.